‎那个门
The gate.
‎不懂 你见过这个门吗
I don't understand. You've seen this before?
‎-不算是  -那到底是什么
-Not exactly. -Then what, exactly?
‎-你只需要知道这很糟  -真的很糟
-All you need to know is it's bad. - It's really bad.
‎差不多世界末日那种糟
Like, end-of-the-human-race-as-we-know-it kind of bad.
‎你怎么知道的
And you know about this how?
史蒂夫 你的苏联的朋友呢
Um, Steve? Where's your Russian friend?
‎糟了
Shit.
‎站住
Halt! Halt!
‎操
Shit.
‎-快走  -操
-Go, go, go, go, go! - Shit.
‎快走 快走
Move! Let's move!
‎糟糕
Go! Shit! Shit, shit, shit!
快走
Go, go, go!
‎天 完蛋了
Holy shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!
完蛋了 这下真的完蛋了
Holy shit! Holy shit! Shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!
完蛋了
Holy shit!
‎-那有警卫 快走  -这边
-Guards! Go! -This way!
操
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
‎-快走  -快点
-Come on! Go, go, go, go, go! - Come on!
‎-操 -这边
-Shit! - This way!
‎-快点  -挡住门
- Come on, quick! - Hold the door!
罗宾
Robin!
‎操
Shit!
‎-帮帮我  -这 快走
- Help me, come on! - Here! Come on, let's go!
‎-快点  -快走 赶快离开这里
-Come on! -Go! Just get out of here!
‎赶快走
Go, come on, now!
‎不行 快找人来帮忙
No! Just go get some help, okay?
‎你在干吗
What are you doing?!
‎快走
Go!
我不会忘记你们的
I won't forget you!
‎快走
Go!
‎他来了
He's here.
‎-糟了  -南希
-Shit. -Nancy!
‎快跑
Run!
‎操
Damn!
‎要命
Come on!
来啊
Hey!
一次只能去两个人
Hey, hey, hey! Two at a time!
‎天
Oh, my God.
‎乔纳森...
Jonathan...
‎不要 南希
No! Nancy!
乔纳森
Jonathan!
‎不要 南希
No, no! Nancy!
‎走楼梯
Stairs.
‎操他妈的
Goddamn it!
‎-天  -什么东西...
-Jesus! -What the f...
‎-快去  -南希
-Go. -Nancy!
‎你没事吧 ‎你没事吧
Are you okay? Are you okay?
是时候了
It's time.
♪ 站起来见见你的兄弟 亲爱的 ♪
♪ Stand up and meet your brother, honey ♪
♪ 不管是不是同肤色 ♪
♪ One color or another ♪
♪ 他都是 ♪
♪ But he's still ♪
♪ 都是你的兄弟 ♪
♪ He's still your brother ♪
♪ 伸出手来 ♪
♪ Reach out and take his hand ♪
♪ 我希望你们都 ♪
♪ I want y'all to ♪
♪ 能让他明白... ♪
♪ Help him understand... ♪
‎先生 抱歉
Hey! Excuse me.
抱歉 抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me.
‎你... 这是干嘛 这是干嘛
What... what are you doing? What's...what's this doing here?
‎-什么  -你的摊位
-What? -Your stand.
占到大路中间了
It's right in the main thoroughfare.
那我摆在哪
Where do you want it, sir?
‎摆在那边的食品摊位区
Over there with the rest of the goddamn food stalls.
能有多难
It isn't rocket science.
屁大点事儿都得我亲自来
Sheesh, do I have to do everything myself?
省警局的朋友
My friends in state PD,
公路巡警都在找
highway patrol, they're all on the lookout.
‎哪都有我的人
I got eyes everywhere.
‎只要他一出现...
The second he pops up...
就有人给我打电话
I get a call.
‎电话
A call?
‎对 电话
Yes. A call.
‎你们还想让我怎么做
I mean, what more do you people want me to do?
‎我们想让你找到他
We want you to find him.
‎我跟你把话说清楚
Let me explain something to you.
‎那人是个白痴
This man is a moron, okay?
‎开辆黄色敞篷车到处乱窜
He's driving around in a yellow convertible, for Christ's sakes.
瞎子才看不见
He sticks out like a sore thumb.
‎我会找到他的
I will find him.
‎我找到了的话
And, when I do,
还烦请您多叫几个帮手一起
may I suggest you bring some backup with you this time?
‎-多叫几个帮手  -苏联同志什么的
-Backup. -Some comrades.
‎因为上次 你可没抓住他
Since last time, he got the better of you
‎求求你...
Please...
‎我...我不是故意的
I... I didn't mean that.
‎你... 你不用带帮手
You...You don't need backup.
都是因为你
This man is your fault,
他才跑了
your problem.
你能活着 就不错了
You're lucky you still breathe.
踩了狗屎运了
Very lucky.
‎求求你
Please.
‎对不起
I'm sorry.
‎我... 我态度不好
I... I have a bad temper.
‎我需要看看医生
I'm going to therapy.
给你一天时间 找到这个人
You have one day to find this man for me.
‎听明白的话 就点头
Nod if you understand.
‎两个皇堡
Two Whoppers,
番茄酱 大包薯条
extra ketchup, large fry,
‎一包红万宝路
pack of Marlboro Reds,
‎还有一杯大杯...
and one extra-large...
思乐冰
Slurpee.
‎汉堡王可没跟七十一便利店挨着
Burger King is nowhere near the 7-Eleven, by the way.
‎我也没说
Never said it was.
‎再试试 乔伊斯
Let's try this again. Joyce.
阿列克谢
Alexei,
那些发电机
the generators,
‎在给什么提供电力
what are they powering?
‎告诉他 我们知道不是星城购物中心
And tell him that we know it is not the Starcourt Mall,
让他别说些没用的
so he can stop selling us that crap.
‎你工作地方的那些发电机 ‎在给什么提供电力
Those generators you were working on, what are you powering?
‎我们知道不是购物中心
We know it's not the mall.
‎这个草莓味的难喝死了
This tastes like shit strawberry.
‎-他说什么  -他说
-What'd he say? -He says,
‎"草莓味的"
"It's strawberry."
什么意思
I'm sorry?
‎他的...思乐冰
His... Slurpee.
‎他说是草莓口味
He says it's strawberry.
‎那怎么了
So what?
‎霍珀 他说了 要樱桃味的
Hop, he did ask for cherry.
‎他们没有樱桃味的
Well, they didn't have cherry.
没有
They didn't have it.
这不重要
And it doesn't matter,
‎因为尝起来都差不多
because it all tastes the same, okay?
‎都是加了冰的糖水 你告诉他
It is sugar on ice. You tell him that.
‎告诉他什么
Tell him what?
‎你告诉他味道都他妈的差不多
You tell him that it all tastes the goddamn same!
‎味道都差不多
It's all the same.
都是加了冰的糖水 差不多
Sugar on ice. No difference.
跟那个傻逼说 差多了
Tell that stupid man it is not the same in the slightest,
‎我要樱桃味的
and I would like the cherry I requested.
‎他说不一样
He respectfully disagrees.
差太多了
It's not the same at all,
‎他想要...
and he would like...
樱桃味的
cherry.
‎是吗 你告诉他... 他想得美
Oh, yeah? You tell him... he can forget it.
‎他说你想得美 没有樱桃味的
He says forget it. No cherry.
‎没有樱桃味的 就没得谈
No cherry, no deal.
‎他说
He says,
"没有樱桃味的...
"No cherry...
‎就没得谈"
no deal."
没得谈
Yeah.
操
Oh, shit!
不要 霍珀
No, Hop
‎等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
-我不会伤害他的 -‎你在干吗
-I'm not gonna hurt him! - What are you doing?
‎别打了
Come on! Come on!
‎我给他个机会
I'm just giving him an opportunity
‎让他去买...
to get his own damn...
‎他樱桃味的思乐冰
cherry Slurpee!
吉姆 那人是我们美国的敌人
Jim, that man is an enemy of the state.
‎对 我们被他整了一天
Yeah, who's been jerking us around for a full day!
‎我买给他樱桃味思乐冰 然后呢
I get him his cherry Slurpee, then what?
‎他再要架直升机  开到他自己的小岛上 我也得同意吗
He wants a helicopter to charter him to his own private island.
‎我跟这种混蛋
I have dealt with assholes like this
打了一辈子的交道
my entire life.
‎昨天在树林里 ‎他本来可以逃跑
Yesterday in the woods, he could've escaped,
可是他没有
but he didn't.
‎他留下来了
He stuck with us.
‎你说是为什么
Why do you think that is?
因为他害怕...
It's because...
‎他害怕
he's scared.
‎不是怕我们
He's scared.
‎而是怕
Not of us,
那些人
of them.
‎他害怕那个苏联大高个
He's scared of that seven-foot-tall Russian freak
不费吹灰之力就能杀了我们
who could've killed him just as easily as us.
‎苏联佬知道
Smirnoff knows
如果他安然无恙地回去了
that if he runs back to his comrades without a scratch on him,
‎那些人就会觉得他出卖了他们
they're gonna think that he spilled his guts.
‎不管怎么样 我们…
So, whether he likes it or not, we...
才是他坚强的后盾
are the best chance he's got.
‎我打赌 半分钟 他就会来敲门
I give him 30 seconds before he comes knocking on that door,
好声好气地
right back into our arms,
跟我们说话
with a new sense of humility.
♪ 我再也无法忍受 ♪
♪ I don't wanna take it anymore ♪
‎吉姆
Jim...
他好像在开车
I, uh, believe he has started the car.
‎霍珀
Hopper.
‎他在测试我们 吓唬吓唬我
You know, testing us. He's just calling my bluff.
♪ 因为我为了生活 如此努力 ♪
♪ 'Cause I work so hard To make it every day ♪
‎他把车开走了
I believe he is now driving away.
‎吉姆 起来
Jim. Jim, move.
-乔伊斯  -起来 起来
-Joyce, Joyce -Move, move, move!
♪ 很难说 ♪
♪ And it's hard to say ♪
♪ 有什么永远不会变 ♪
♪ Just how some things never change ♪
♪ 很难说 ♪
♪ And it's hard to find ♪
♪ 划清界线有什么好 ♪
♪ Any strength to draw the line ♪
♪ 浑身燥热 劲舞狂欢 ♪
♪ Ooh, I'm just burning Doin' the neutron dance ♪
♪ I'm just burning Doin' the neutron dance ♪
♪ 我知道我也会有一盆金 ♪
♪ I know there's a pot of gold for me ♪
♪ 我只需要相信... ♪
♪ All I've got to do is just believe... ♪
♪ 劲舞狂欢 ♪
♪ Doin' the neutron dance ♪
♪ 浑身燥热... ♪
♪ And I'm just burning... ♪
‎他刚说什么
I'm sorry, what did he say?
‎他说他也喜欢草莓味的
He says he likes strawberry, too.
♪ 浑身燥热 双脚腾空 ♪
♪ I'm just burning In my feet ♪
♪ 劲舞狂欢 ♪
♪ Doin' the neutron dance ♪
‎我们放火 把那地方烧了
So, when we set fire to the hub,
‎把魔狗引开 好让小伊关上门
we drew the Demodogs away so El could close the gate.
可是 不知道怎么回事
But now, for some insane reason,
‎苏联人竟然想把门再打开
the Russians appear to be trying to reopen it,
‎我们拼了老命把门关上  那不就白费力气了吗
which just destroys everything we risked our lives for.
"我们" 包括卢卡斯吗
By "We," You're including Lucas?
‎当然包括
Yes, of course.
‎你刚说的 卢卡斯都在场吗
So, all that shit you told me, Lucas was there?
‎-对  -我哥  卢卡斯·查尔斯·辛克莱
-Yeah. -My brother, Lucas Charles Sinclair?
‎对
Yes!
‎我不信
I don't believe you.
我说的关于小伊和门的事
Wait, so you believe everything about El and the gate
‎还有魔狗和夺心魔的事 你都信
and the Demodogs and the Mind Flayer,
‎可不信你哥哥在场
but you question your brother's involvement?
对
That's correct.
‎能理解
Makes total sense.
‎-你要帮忙吗  -不用
-Um, you need help with that? -No.
‎你研究了那么久
Well, I mean, it's taking a while,
-所以... -闭嘴 福尔摩斯
-so... -Yeah, no shit, Sherlock.
如果我们
All right, so if we don't
关不掉这些风扇
find a more efficient method to stop these fans,
‎那就找不到人来救我们
we're never gonna find help,
你那卖冰淇淋的朋友也完蛋了
and your ice cream buddies are screwed.
‎你那态度能找到人来帮忙才见鬼了
Yeah, with that attitude, they are. Jee-zus!
实话实说
I'm just being realistic.
‎我们九个小时走了大概五百米
I mean, we've made it about point-three miles in nine hours.
‎然后过那个地道 用三个小时
Then we had to walk three hours down that tunnel,
‎估计回到电梯那要走十六公里
so I'd estimate ten miles back to the elevator,
‎大概需要走十二天半
which should take us approximately twelve-and-a-half days.
‎你刚才是心算的吗
Did you just do all of that in your head?
我对数字比较在行
I'm good with numbers.
‎天 你是个怪胎
Holy shit. You're a nerd.
‎你说什么
Come again?
‎你... 是...个...怪胎
You... are... a... nerd.
‎你最好收回那句话 怪胎
Okay, you better take that back, nerd.
事实怎么收回去
Can't put the truth back in the box.
‎-那不是事实  -给你几个事实你看看
-But it's not the truth. -Let's examine the facts, shall we?
‎第一 你是数学天才
you're a math whiz, apparently.
那就是小学数学
That was a pretty straightforward equation.
‎第二 你是政治狂
Fact number two: you're a political junkie.
‎就因为我不觉得共产主义是种意识形态...
Just because I don't agree with Communism as an ideology...
‎第三个 你喜欢"小马宝莉"
Fact number three: you love My Little Pony.
‎这跟"小马宝莉"有什么关系
And what does My Little Pony have to do with this?
‎我们来一起回顾下"小马宝莉"最近的一次探险吧
Ah, let's recall the ponies' latest adventure, shall we?
‎邪恶的半人马和提雷克
The evil centaur team and Tirek
‎在午夜城堡把苹果嘉儿变成条龙
turns Applejack into a dragon at Midnight Castle,
‎梅根和其他的小马 ‎只好用穆奇克的魔法
and then Megan and the other ponies have to use Moochick's magic
‎打败他的黑暗彩虹
to defeat his rainbow of darkness,
‎拯救了他们 他们就不用一辈子当奴隶了
saving them from a lifetime of enslavement.
‎世上所有的粉红迷都不否认
All the pink in the world can't disguise the irrefutable fact
‎半人马 城堡 龙和魔法 ‎
that centaurs and castles and dragons and magic
都是怪胎的标配
are all standard nerd tropes.
‎所以"小马宝莉"是怪胎
Ergo, My Little Pony is nerdy.
‎所以你 艾丽卡
Ergo, you, Erica,
是怪胎
are a nerd.
‎你怎么这么了解"小马宝莉"
And how do you know so much about My Little Pony?
‎因为我是…
Because I'm...
‎个怪胎
a nerd.
‎走吧...
Let's go...
怪胎
nerd.
‎你…
You...
好疼
That one stung.
‎谁派你来的
Who do you work for?
说了好几遍了 ‎我在水手冰淇淋店打工
For the millionth time, I work at Scoops Ahoy!
‎水手冰淇淋
Scoops Ahoy.
打我干吗
What the hell?!
‎看我的衣服
Look at my outfit!
你以为我想穿成这样吗
You think I just wear this?!
‎间谍会穿水手服吗
Think I'm a spy in a sailor's uniform?
‎你怎么进来的
How did you get in?
跟你说了
I already told you.
‎我说过了
I told you before.
‎有批货没到
My delivery didn't come,
‎我和我朋友以为
and my friends and I, we
落在了卸货的地方了
thought that it was left at the loading dock,
‎我们进去之后 才发现那是电梯
so we went in the room, and then it turned into an elevator,
‎然后... 电梯突然掉下来
and then... and then we dropped and then,
‎等我 睁开眼
next thing we know, I open my eyes,
我才发现...
and we're in this...
我们在这个神奇的地方
wonderful facility.
我对天发誓
But I swear to God,
‎没人知道 也没人看见
nobody knows about us, nobody saw us.
‎你能直接放我们走吗
You could just let us go, all right?
‎我不会告诉别人这件事
And I'm not gonna tell anybody about this, okay?
‎人生多不易 且行且珍惜
Shit happens, life goes on.
‎冰... ‎冰淇淋
Ice... ice cream.
‎冰淇淋
Ice cream, okay?
你们知道冰淇淋吧 大家都喜欢吃冰淇淋
You guys know what ice cream is. Everybody loves ice cream.
我不知道
I don't know if you have
‎苏联有没有冰淇淋 或者你们把那当成意式冰淇淋
Russian ice cream or if that's considered gelato.
‎管他什么是什么 但不管你们要什么
I don't know what's what, but whatever you guys want, seriously.
‎奶油糖果号 你们一定要吃吃看
USS Butterscotch, I mean, you gotta try it.
‎我告诉你们 好吃到爆
It is out of this world, I'm telling ya!
‎我喜欢这个家伙
I like this guy!
‎"奶油... 糖果号"
"USS... Butterscotch."
谁派你来的
Who do you work for?
‎拜托 不会吧
Oh, come on. No, no! No, seriously
‎放开我
Get your hands off me!
‎那个…
Hey...
‎史蒂夫
Steve?
‎史蒂夫 ‎史蒂夫
Steve? Steve?
‎史蒂夫
Steve?
你对他做了什么 你做了什么
What did you do to him? What did you do?
‎让他们坐到椅子上
Put them in the chairs.
‎别碰我…
Don't touch me!
‎史蒂夫...
Steve...
‎‎史蒂夫 醒醒 ‎史蒂夫
Steve, wake up. Steve?
‎你做了什么
What did you do?!
‎别碰他
Don't touch him.
‎史蒂夫 ‎史蒂夫 能听见吗
Steve? Steve, can you hear me?
‎你朋友生病了 该看医生了
I think your friend need a doctor.
‎幸好...
Good thing...
‎我们这有最好的医生
we have the very best.
‎你会后悔的 小婊子
You are going to regret that, little bitch.
混蛋
Bastards.
放我们出去
Let us outta here!
‎混蛋 放我们出去
Bastards! Let us out! Let us out!
她在里面那么久 不好吧
It can't be good for her to be in there for this long.
‎迈克 你别紧张
Mike, you need to relax.
万一伤到她脑袋怎么办
What if she gets brain damage or something?
‎糟糕 他说的
Oh, shit. Is that, like,
-是真的吗 ‎ -不会 他乱说的
-a real thing? -No, it's not. He made it up.
迈克不知道他自己在说什么
Mike doesn't know what he's talking about.
‎-那你就知道吗  -不是 我…
-Oh, and you do? -No, I...
‎对 "霍金斯邮报"
Yes, from The Hawkins Post.
‎我...我几天前打过...
I... I called a couple days ago about the...
对...
Yes, yes, um...
‎我就是...跟踪调查一下
I was just... following
有没有丢什么东西
up to see if anything else had gone missing,
‎或者…好吧
or if... Okay.
‎抱歉打扰了…
Um, sorry to bother
‎-接下来是哪个  -没了
- Who's next? - There is no next.
‎除非你想随便打打
Unless you want to start calling random people's homes.
‎-不应该  -这件事里哪部分是应该的
-It doesn't make sense. -What part of any of this makes sense?
有规律的 他们做事都有规律的
There's a pattern, okay? A consistency to their behavior.
‎一开始的时候 他们吃这些化学物
They've been feeding on these chemicals since this started,
然后...‎他们突然就不吃了吗
and...and, what, they just stop, out of the blue?
‎也许他们该有的化学物都有了
Maybe they have all the chemicals they need.
‎也许他们都变成那种东西了
Maybe they've all turned into those... things.
‎源头在哪
But what about the source?
‎夺心魔突然就不附在人身上了吗
I mean, did the Mind Flayer just suddenly stop infecting people?
‎就算被夺心的人现在是怪物 ‎为什么小伊找不到他们
And even if the flayed are monsters now, why can't El find them?
‎你们能当下裁判吗
Okay, can you guys settle an argument for us?
‎谁应该决定小伊的极限
Who do you think should decide El's limits?
迈克还是伊莱雯自己
Mike or Eleven?
‎你怎么这么问 太心机了吧
The way that you frame that is such bullshit.
‎不是心机 迈克 ‎问题就出在这
It's not bullshit, Mike. This is your whole problem.
所以她才会把你甩了
And it's also precisely the reason why she dumped your ass.
‎你被小伊甩了吗
El dumped you?
‎对 因为麦克斯想着怎么整我
Yeah, because she is conspiring against me.
她把小伊带坏了
She's corrupting her.
没有 是开导她
No, enlightening her.
‎事实是 她不是你的私有物
The fact is, she's not yours.
‎她是独立的人 能自己做决定
She's her own person, fully capable of making her own decisions.
‎她心甘情愿冒生命危险
She's risking her life for no reason.
心甘情愿
For no reason?
迈克 天知道被夺了心的人在做什么
Mike, the flayed are out there doing God knows what.
‎-杀人 夺心…  -变形成怪物
-Killing, flaying... -Transforming into monsters.
‎小伊不是笨蛋
And El's not stupid.
‎她比我们更了解自己的能力
She knows her abilities better than any of us.
‎-没错 谢谢  -她是独立的人
-Exactly, thank you. -And she is her own person.
‎-没错  -有自己的自由意志
-Exactly. -With her own free will.
‎没错
Exactly.
‎小伊拯救世界两次 迈克还不信任她
El has saved the world twice, and Mike still doesn't trust her.
‎你还好意思说信任吗
You wanna talk about trust,
你让伊莱雯监视我们
really? After you made Eleven spy on us?
‎-等等 什么  -她没告诉你吗
-Wait, what? -Oh, she didn't tell you this?
‎-没有  -你女朋友利用小伊的能力
-No. -Your girlfriend used El's powers
‎-监视我们  -不是 我没有逼她
-to spy on us. -No, no, no, I did not make her.
她自己想知道
It was her idea.
‎我们为什么要讨论这件事
And why are we even talking about this, seriously?
‎谁在乎
Yeah, who cares?
‎-我在乎  -对
-I care. -Yeah.
‎女朋友不说谎
I guess girlfriends don't lie,
-她们爱监视  -我们闹着玩的
-they spy.  -We were just joking around.
如果我在拉大屎
Wouldn't it've been so funny
或者干其他的 那不是很搞笑吗
if I was taking a massive shit or something?
‎-你没有啊  -如果呢
-You weren't. -But what if I was?
‎-那就太恶心了  -说真的 迈克
-Then gross! -Seriously, Mike?
‎我只是想说
I'm just trying to demonstrate
麦克思滥用伊莱雯的能力
how careless Max is with Eleven's powers.
‎其实 你们都一样
In fact, how careless all of you are.
‎你们把她
You're treating her like
当机器使 可她不是
some kind of machine when she's not a machine,
‎我不想她牺牲自己 去找被夺心的人
and I don't want her to die looking for the flayed
‎他们肯定都从地球上消失了
when they've obviously vanished off the face of the Earth.
‎所以我们能换个计划吗
So can we please just come up with a new plan
因为我爱她 ‎我不能再失去她了
because I love her and I can't lose her again.
‎怎么了
What's going on?
‎没事
Nothing. Nothing.
‎只是家庭讨论
Just a family discussion.
好吧
Oh.
‎我找到他了
I found him.
‎找到谁了
Found who?
‎他说那个是钥匙 ‎钥匙能产生强大的能量
He calls it the key, and this key emits a great energy.
‎需要很多能量 电
It requires much strength, power.
你们发现的那些房子
Those houses, like the one you found,
‎附近都有变压器
they're located near, uh, transformers.
‎他们偷你们镇上的电
They're stealing from your town's power grid.
‎为什么在这做这个钥匙
Why build this key here?
‎不在苏联做
Why are they not doing this in their own backyard?
想把我们炸成碎片吗
What are they trying to do, blow us to smithereens?
‎以前 在苏联 有很多这种钥匙
There were many of these, uh, keys before in Russia,
‎可或多或少都有问题
but they turned out wrong.
‎他们只好来… 来...
They had to come to where the... where the, uh...
‎来哪
Where the what?
‎-我不知道他说的什么  -还以为你讲得很流利
-I don't understand what he's saying. -I thought you were fluent.
‎抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
‎免费翻译 不满意是吗
Are my free translation services not good enough for you?
‎那你可以去投诉啊
Because you can just go ahead and file your complaint right up my ass!
苏联佬在干吗
What is Smirnoff doing?
‎他在示范
He's showing me.
‎这样
Oh, okay.
他说这个吸管
Uh, he says the straw,
‎他们用它来穿透
they're using it to penetrate a hole
‎一个箱子吗
in... A box?
‎抱歉 抱歉
Okay, sorry, sorry.
‎吸管代表钥匙 能产生巨大的能量
The straw represents the key, which emits a great energy.
‎他们用这个能量...
They're using this energy...
‎穿透这个屏障
to break through a barrier,
‎打开...
to open...
‎一个门
a doorway.
一个连接两个世界的门
A doorway between worlds.
‎可看来这个钥匙只是解开等式的一半
But it seems this key was only half the equation.
‎地点... 正确的地点是另一半
Location...Location was the other half.
‎怎么了
Oh, what
‎在霍金斯 这个门被打开过一次
In Hawkins, this door had been opened once.
‎还在…
It was still...
‎愈合
healing.
‎天
Jesus Christ.
‎所以这个门现在已经打开了吗
So, this door is open now?
‎他说门…
He says it is...
‎正在打开
opening.
‎-你要去哪  -打电话给孩子们
-Where are you going? -To call our children.
‎现在能看"兔八哥"了吗
Can we watch Looney Tunes now?
不能
Nyet.
‎-你要找什么  -威士忌
-Can I help you with something? -Whiskey.
‎-你有威士忌吗  -没 可我有伏特加
-You have whiskey? -No, but I do have vodka.
‎如果这个钥匙能被启动
If there's a way to start this key,
‎那就能被关掉 对吧
there's gotta be a way to stop it, yeah?
‎关掉
Turn it off?
‎-对  -对吗
-Right. -Right?
能关掉钥匙吗
The key, is there a way to turn it off?
‎他说 "当然能关掉
He says, "Of course he could turn it off. Could...
哪有‎爱迪生关不掉的灯 ‎贝尔挂不断的电话"
Edison not turn off a lamp, could Bell not hang up a phone?"
‎狂什么狂 "不过…"
Cocky bastard. "But..."
‎不过什么
But what?
‎不过他现在
But he is now...
"裸露了"
"Naked."
‎抱歉 "身份暴露了" 折中一下
Sorry, "Exposed." Compromised.
‎我带你去那
Hey, I will get you there.
‎带你去找钥匙
I will get you to your key.
‎能不能问问他笑什么
You wanna ask him what the hell's so funny about that?
‎他说他喜欢你的勇气
He says he likes your courage.
你让他想到…
You remind him of a...
‎胖兰博[第一滴血 史泰龙角色名]
...fat Rambo.
他说瘦兰博都进不去
But he says that even thin Rambo couldn't get there.
‎钥匙在一个地堡里
This key, it is in an underground fortress
是最优秀的苏联人设计的
designed by the greatest Russian minds,
‎由最英勇的战士看守着
guarded by their greatest warriors.
‎要混进去是…
Breaking in is...
‎不可能的事
impossible.
到了
Jackpot.
帅呆了
Oh-ho-ho!
‎你会开车吗
Do you even know how to drive?
‎能有多难 麦克斯都会
How hard can it be? Max did it.
‎-快点  -你真的觉得
- Aw, come on. -You seriously thought
‎-他们不会把钥匙带走吗 -一定有备用钥匙
-they'd just leave keys in there? -There's gotta be a spare.
‎-达斯汀  -怎么了
- Hey, Dustin? -Yeah?
‎你说那个魔神有多大来着
How big did you say that Demogorgon was?
‎很大 快三米 怎么了
Big. Nine feet or so. Why?
‎找到了
Found 'em.
艾丽卡
Erica?
‎那是什么东西
What the hell is that?!
‎致命武器
A deadly weapon.
可能有用
Could be useful.
‎-有什么用  -你觉得呢
-For what? -What do you think?
‎击倒共产党 救你的朋友
Taking down Commies, saving your friends.
‎还以为你会现实点 怪胎
Thought you were more realistic than that, nerd.
‎我们都不知道他们在哪
We don't even know where they are,
‎就算我们知道 那也有很多警卫
and even if we did, there are a million guards up there
‎拿的武器都比那个更致命
with weapons way deadlier than that.
救他们最好的办法 ‎
The best thing we can do
就是离开这 找人帮忙
for them is to get out of here and find help.
‎小心点
Easy with that.
‎我们和他们才能保命
Our chance of surviving, and theirs, rises substantially.
‎相信我 拜托
Just trust me on this. Please?
‎救命
Help!
‎-救命  -能别喊了吗
-Help! -Hey, would you stop yelling?
‎史蒂夫 天
Steve! Oh, my God!
‎史蒂夫...
Steve...
‎你没事吧
Are...Are you okay?
耳鸣 不太能呼吸过来
My ears are ringing, and I can't really breathe,
‎眼珠好像也要掉出来了
my eye feels like it's about to pop out of my skull,
‎除了这 我还不错吧
but, you know, apart from that, I'm doing pretty good.
‎好消息是他们给你叫医生了
Well, the good news is that they're calling you a doctor.
‎就是在这看的吗
Is this his place of work?
这地方不错
I love the vibe.
挺好的
Charming.
‎还用你说
Yeah, tell me about it. So, okay,
‎看到右边
do you see that table over
那张桌子了吗 ‎ 不是 你的右边
there to your right? No, your other right.
‎-看到了 -好的
-Oh. -Yeah, okay.
-看到剪刀了吗 -看到了
-And do you see those scissors? -Uh-huh.
‎好 如果我们
Yeah, well, I think that if we
一块动 ‎应该能挪到那
move at the same time, we could get over there,
‎然后我能
and then maybe I could
踢到桌子 然后剪刀掉到你腿上
kick the table and knock them into your lap.
‎‎-我剪断绳子  -对 我们就能离开这
-And I could cut the binds. -Yeah, and we could get out of here.
-了解 能做到  -对‎
-Gotcha. Okay, yeah, we can do that. -Yeah.
‎那些白痴 竟然把剪刀放在这
Those morons. They left scissors in here?
-对 白痴  -大白痴
-Yeah, morons. -Total morons.
-好的 -好
-Okay. -Okay, so,
‎我数到三 跳起来
on the count of three, we're gonna hop.
‎-好 数到三跳 了解  -好
-Okay, good, hop on three. I gotcha. -All right.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
‎-好 有用  -好
-Okay, that worked. -Okay.
‎‎-好 再试一次  -好
-All right. Uh, let's try again. -Right.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
‎‎-天 可以可以  -近了 准备好了吗
-Holy shit, this is gonna work! -We're close. Ready?
‎好 一 二 三
Okay, one, two, three.
‎‎没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
‎别哭 罗宾
Don't cry. Robin.
‎‎你在笑吗
Are you laughing?
‎-对  -天啊
-Yeah. -Jesus!
‎对不起
I'm sorry!
对不起 只是…
I'm so sorry. It's just...
‎‎我不敢相信...
I can't believe...
‎我会 跟发胶男史蒂夫·哈林顿 ‎
I'm gonna die in a secret Russian base
死在苏联的秘密基地里
with Steve "The Hair" Harrington.
‎-太扯了  -我们不会死的
-It's just too trippy, man. -We're not gonna die.
‎我们会逃出去的‎
We're gonna get out of here, okay?
你让我想一下
Just... You gotta let me just think for a second.
‎你还记得 高二克里克老师的历史课吗
Do you remember, um, Mrs. Click's sophomore history class?
‎什么
What?
‎咔嗒咔嗒老师
Mrs. Clickity-Clackity.
‎我们都那样叫她
That's what us band dweebs called her.
‎第一堂课
It was first period,
‎星期二和星期四 所以你每次都迟到
Tuesdays and Thursdays, so you were always late.
‎你早饭都一样
And you always had the same breakfast.
‎培根 鸡蛋 带芝士芝麻的百吉饼
Bacon, egg, and cheese on a sesame bagel.
‎我坐在你后面
I sat behind you
‎一周两天 坐了一年
two days a week for a year.
‎搞笑先生
Mister Funny.
‎耍酷先生
Mister Cool.
‎霍金斯高中之王
The King of Hawkins High himself.
‎你还记得我们一起上过那堂课吗
Do you even remember me from that class?
‎你当然不记得
Of course you don't.
‎你真是个混蛋 你知道吗
You were a real asshole, you know that?
‎我知道
Yeah, I know.
‎不过不重要
But it didn't even matter.
‎你是混蛋没关系
It didn't matter that you were an ass.
‎我还是...
I was still...
很喜欢你
obsessed with you.
虽然我们都不是什么成功人士
Even though all of us losers pretend to be above it all,
可我们还是想成为好人缘的...
we still just wanna be popular...
合群的
accepted,
正常人
normal.
这么跟你说
If it makes you feel any better,
其实没什么好的
having those things isn't all that great.
‎说真的
Seriously.
‎只会让我迷茫
It just baffles me.
大家跟你说的那些重要的事
Everything that people tell you is important,
那些
everything that people
‎你应该关心的事 都只是...
say you should care about, it's all just...
...胡扯的
...bullshit.
经验是从经历里学来的 不是吗
But I guess you gotta mess up to figure things out, right?
‎希望吧
I hope so.
‎我觉得我从小到大好像…
I feel like my whole life has been...
错得很离谱
one big error.
说得对
Yep.
起码不会比现在惨
At least it can't get any more messed up than this.
‎真希望在克里克的课上就认识你
You know, I wish I'd known you in Click's class.
‎-是吗  -真的
-Yeah? -Really, I do.
可能有了你 我那门课就不会挂
Maybe you could've helped me pass the class.
‎我就不会在这
Maybe instead of being here,
现在应该准备去上大学了
I'd be on my way to college right now.
‎那我就不会知道
And I would have no idea
‎我们下面住满了邪恶的苏联人
that there were evil Russians beneath our feet,
‎我会开开心心
and I would be happily
跟另一个笨蛋 ‎一起舀冰淇淋
slinging ice cream with some other schmuck.
‎老实说
Gotta say, though,
我喜欢当你的笨蛋
I liked being your schmuck.
‎很开心
It was fun while it lasted.
‎是啊
It was.
‎你们两个准备去哪
Where were you two going?
‎这次说实话吧
Try telling the truth this time, yes?
‎这样柴可夫医生看完病 你们就不会那么痛苦了
It will make your visit with Dr. Zharkov less painful.
‎等等 等等 等等
Wait a second. Wait. Hold on.
‎等等 那是什么
Okay! Wait, wait, wait! What is that thing?
‎帮你说实话
It will help you talk.
‎那玩意儿消毒了吗
Did you even clean that thing?!
‎他现在在干吗
What's he doing now?
‎那是不是不正常
And that's not normal, right?
比利独立日的时候不出门吗
Billy staying in his room on the Fourth of July?
‎那不正常
No, that's not normal.
‎他想让我们找到他
He wants us to find him.
‎对 我怕的就是这
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
‎如果我们去找比利 ‎其他被夺心的人就知道我们在哪了
If we go to Billy, then the rest of the flayed know where we are.
‎我也觉得这是陷阱 我们就中计了
It's a trap, I agree. We'll be ambushed.
‎这一点都不意外
We won't be surprised.
‎我们知道他们会来
We'll know that they're coming,
我们好好教训他们一顿
and we will kick their flayed butts.
‎小伊好好教训他们一顿
You mean El will kick their butts.
‎爸爸
Papa!
‎不要
No.
‎彩虹 右三左四
Rainbow. Three to the right, four to the left.
向日葵 彩虹
Sunflower. Rainbow.
‎-太冒险了  -对 也没必要
- It's too risky. - Yeah, and unnecessary.
把被夺心的人杀掉 也阻止不了夺心魔
Killing the flayed won't stop the Mind Flayer.
‎我们要找到他们是从哪蔓延的
We have to find out where it's spreading from.
‎我们要找到源头
We have to find the source.
‎比利知道
Billy knows it.
‎比利去过那
Billy's been there.
‎去过源头
To the source.
‎-对 可…  -我知道是陷阱
-Yeah, but... -It's a trap. I know.
‎我们不能去找比利
We can't go to Billy,
还有个方法
but I think there's another way.
我看看他去过哪
A way for me to see where he's been.
‎小伊 我知道你觉得自己一定得这么做 不过别勉强自己
El, I know you think you have to do this, but you don't.
‎你之前做过一次
It's just, you've only done this before once.
‎还有你妈 她爱你
And your mom, she loved you,
‎想让你知道发生了什么
and wanted you to know what happened.
‎比利的心... 坏掉了 生病了
And Billy's mind is... is sick, diseased.
‎夺心魔控制了他
The Mind Flayer is in him.
‎他伤害不了我
He can't hurt me.
‎那个世界里不会
Not in there.
‎谁也说不准
We don't know that.
迈克
Mike.
‎你要相信我
I need you to trust me.
当然
Yeah.
‎小心点
Just... be careful.
‎比利
Billy.
‎能听见我说话吗
Can you hear me?
‎我想看看
I want to see.
‎想知道发生了什么
I want to see what happened.
‎出事了
Something's wrong.
‎住手 不要
Stop! No! No! No!
不要
No!
‎小伊 你还好吗
El, are you okay?
‎你没事吧
Are you okay?
‎我没事
I'm okay.
‎怎么了
What's going on?
‎我... 在海滩上
I'm... on a beach.
‎好 我虽然有点傻
Okay, I may be dense,
不过 我想
but the last I checked,
‎霍金斯没有海滩
there weren't any beaches in Hawkins.
‎你还看到什么
What else do you see?
‎一个女人
A woman.
‎她…
She's...
‎很漂亮
pretty.
‎我…
I...
‎她好像在看我
I think she's looking at me.
‎好棒
Woo!
真棒
Yeah!
‎你做到了
You did it!
‎有个...
There's...
小男孩
a boy.
看见了吗
Did you see that?
‎我看见了
Yeah, I saw that!
至少有两米吧
That was at least seven feet.
‎我不知道那是什么 ‎不过我差点吓出心脏病了
I don't know what it was, but it almost gave me a heart attack.
‎再玩十分钟吧
Ten more minutes?
‎-好吧 十分钟  -好的
-Yeah, okay, ten more minutes. -Okay.
如果再不回去的话 爸爸生气了
But any longer than that, Dad's gonna be mad, okay?
‎好的
Okay!
‎比利
Billy?
‎小心激流
Watch out for rip currents!
‎知道啦
I know.
‎是比利
It's Billy.
‎在加利福尼亚省
It's California.
‎是段回忆
It's a memory.
‎我好像看到了
I think I see it.
‎源头
The source.
‎两分钟 吉姆
Two minutes, Jim.
‎那是安全线
It's a secure line, but any
超过两分钟 ‎他们就能查到你
longer than that and they could trace you.
‎我就是要他们查到我
Yeah, I want 'em to trace me.
什么
What?
‎费城公共图书馆
Philadelphia Public Library.
‎我是吉姆·霍珀...
This is Jim Hopper...
‎霍金斯的警长
uh... police chief, Hawkins.
这个号码是萨姆·欧文斯博士给我的
I got this number from Dr. Sam Owens.
‎你的个人识别码是什么
What is your identification code?
个人识别码
Identification code?
‎你不知道吗
You don't know it?
开什么玩笑
You must be joking.
‎找到了 找到了
Oh, no, no, I got it, I got it.
找到了
I got it.
‎你把个人识别码写下来放在皮夹里吗
You wrote it down and kept it in your wallet?
‎"古战车" 听着
"Antique Chariot." Listen.
‎告诉欧文斯 苏联佬们正在开门
Um, tell Owens that the Russkies are opening the gate.
‎他知道什么意思 ‎
Now, he'll know what that means.
不是苏联佬们 是门
Not about the Russkies, but about the gate.
‎告诉他 在星城购物中心有个入口
Tell him that there's an entrance at Starcourt Mall.
‎我知道怎么进去
I know how to get in,
‎不过我需要人支援 很多很多人支援
but I need backup, a lot of backup.
‎让他打电给我 号码是618-625-8313
Have him call me back here at 618-625-8313.
‎我会转告给他的
Your message will be relayed.
‎-现在怎么办  -现在我们…
-So, now what? -Now, we, uh...
‎只能等
we wait.
‎你把我暴露了 吉姆
You compromised me, Jim.
你知道这样我就暴露了吧 我还得再搬家
You do realize that, don't you? I'm gonna have to relocate.
‎-要等多久  -等到电话来
-How long do we wait? -As long as it takes.
‎你怎么能这么淡定地坐在那
How can you just sit there being calm?
‎我哪淡定了
I am not calm!
‎我们孩子有危险
Our kids are in danger!
‎你说他们去参加庆祝活动了
You said they were at the festival!
‎那里离门才十分钟车程
Which is, like, ten minutes from the gate!
‎你在干什么 乔伊斯
What are you doing? Joyce?
‎你在干什么
What are you doing?
‎费城公共图书馆
Philadelphia Public Library.
‎你好
Yes, hello.
我是古战车的朋友...
Uh, this is, uh, Antique Chariot's partner...
‎手推车
Wheelbarrow.
我觉得古战车
I don't think Antique Chariot
‎没有讲清楚 我们情况很紧急
properly conveyed the urgency of our situation.
‎你在做什么
What are you doing?
‎我们不能坐在这 一直等电话
Can't just sit around and wait for a call.
‎-太太 请你冷静点  -不要
-Ma'am, I'm gonna need you to stay calm. -No.
‎你好大的胆子 敢敷衍我
Don't you dare patronize me!
‎我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are,
‎管你是什么高级秘书
if you're some glorified secretary or what,
‎如果你不想丢掉饭碗 那就按我说的做
but if you don't wanna lose your job, here's what's gonna happen.
‎我挂掉电话之后
When I hang up,
‎你站起来
you're gonna get up off your ass,
‎找欧文斯告诉他怎么回事
and you're gonna go find Owens and tell him what's going on.
‎我们没时间解释 他也别问
We don't have time to talk about it and neither does he.
‎让他马上
He's gotta get to Hawkins,
带人赶到霍金斯
and he's gotta bring his men right now!
听明白了吗
Do you understand me?
‎是 太太
Yes, yes, ma'am.
‎谢谢 再见
Thank you. And good day.
‎才一分钟 乔伊斯
It's been exactly one minute, Joyce.
‎一分钟也太久了
That's one minute too long.
阿列克谢
Alexei.
‎怎么了
What's going on?
‎我们要走了 嗡嗡
We gotta go. Vroom, vroom.
‎回霍金斯 快点
Back to Hawkins. Come on.
‎快点
Come on.
‎老实说 我什么感觉都没有
Honestly, I don't really feel anything.
‎你呢
Do you?
‎我…觉得还好
I mean, I... I feel fine.
‎-正常  -我... 我也是
-I feel normal. -Yeah, I feel... I feel fine.
‎感觉还挺舒服的
I kinda feel good.
‎-跟你说个秘密吧  -什么
-Wanna know a secret? -What?
‎我挺喜欢的
I like it, too!
‎-感觉很舒服  -白痴 他们打错药了
-I feel good. -Morons. They messed up the drug.
‎他们打错了
They messed it up!
‎-白痴  -白痴
-Morons. Hey, morons! -Morons!
‎-白痴 白 -来人啊
-Moron! Mor -Hey!
来啊
Whoa-oh!
‎不对 我们肯定有问题
Oh, no. There's definitely something wrong with us.
‎有问题
Something's wrong.
‎现在跟你说 我讨厌医生 是不是时机不对
Would now be a good time to tell you that I don't like doctors?
我再问你一次
Let's try this again, yes?
谁派你来的
Who do you work for?
‎水手
Scoops.
水手冰淇淋
Scoops Ahoy.
‎你们怎么找到我们的
How did you find us?
‎误打误撞
Totally by accident.
‎还嘴硬
More lies.
‎-那个闪闪的玩意是什么  -你那个要干吗
-What is that shiny little toy? - Where you going with that, doc?
‎等等 不要 ‎等等
Wait! No! Wait! Wait!
‎有暗号 我们听到暗号了
There was a code! We heard a code!
‎暗号
Code.
‎什么暗号
What code?
"漫长的一周
"The week is long.
‎银猫大开吃戒 ‎只等蓝和黄在西方相遇"
The silver cat feeds when blue meets yellow in the west."
吧啦 吧啦的
Blah, blah, blah.
‎你们到处广播那个傻逼间谍暗号
You broadcast that stupid spy shit all over town,
‎被我们的脑波机收到了
and we picked it up on our Cerebro,
‎我们一天就破解出来了
and we cracked it in a day.
‎一天哦
A day!
‎你们觉得自己聪明得不得了
You think you're so smart,
‎可是 两个舀冰淇淋赚钱的小屁孩
but a couple of kids who scoop ice cream for a living
‎一天就把你们的暗号解出来了 ‎现在大家知道你们在这
cracked your code in a day, and now, people know you're here.
‎谁知道我们在这里 小婊子
Who knows we are here, little bitch?
‎达斯汀知道
Dustin knows.
‎别说 史蒂夫
Hey, Steve?
‎-达斯汀·亨德森知道  -史蒂夫
-Yeah, Dustin Henderson, he knows. -Steve!
‎达斯汀·亨德森
Dustin Henderson.
你们那个卷毛小孩吗
It is your small, curly-haired friend?
‎小卷毛 发质好 ‎有点爆炸头 对 就是他
Oh, curly-haired. Great hair. Small. Kind of like a 'fro. Yeah.
‎他在哪
Where is he?
‎他早跑掉了 大混蛋
He's long gone, you big asshole.
‎他可能会给霍珀打电话
And he's probably calling Hopper,
霍珀再联系美国骑兵
and Hopper's calling the US cavalry.
‎他们派突击队过来 拿着枪过来
They're gonna come in here, commando-style, guns a-blazin',
‎把你们都赶回苏联
and kick your sorry asses back to Russia.
‎你们就完蛋了
You're gonna be two pieces of toast.
‎是吗
Is that so?
‎对
Yeah.
亨德森
Hey! Henderson!
‎太神了 我刚刚说到你
That's crazy, I was just talking about you.
‎-天 -赶紧准备跑
-Oh, my God! -Get ready to run.
‎比利 站住
Hey! Billy, stop!
‎你怎么回事 我们怎么说的
What the hell is wrong with you? What did we talk about, huh?
‎你得挥出去
You gotta slide!
‎-我知道  -等等
- I know. -Wait.
‎-你是怕受伤吗  -不是
-Afraid you're gonna get hurt, is that it? -No.
‎那是什么 什么
Well, what then? What?
‎我儿子是个孬种
What did I raise, a pussy for a son?
‎-别骂我  -站住
-Leave me alone! -Hey!
跑啊 你就会逃避
That's right, run! Like you always do!
‎你昨晚去哪了 去哪了
Where were you last night? Where were you?
‎-我说了 我去找温迪了  -别骗我了
- I told you, I was with Wendy. - Stop lying to me!
‎-我没骗你  -你是不是又去找他了
- I'm not lying to you! -You saw him again, didn't you?
‎-是不是  -走开
-Didn't you?! -Get away from me!
‎-叫你走开  -你...这个妓女
-I said, get away! -You... You whore!
‎-住手  -臭女人
-Stop it! -Bitch!
‎-不要打她  -不要
-Don't hurt her! -No!
‎-不要打她  -混蛋
-Don't hurt her! - You bastard!
‎妈妈
Mom!
‎我不懂 为什么不回家
I don't understand. Why not?
‎拜托 妈妈 别这样
Please, Mom, don't do this.
‎求求你回家吧
Please come home.
‎不要 多久 多久
No. How long? How long?!
‎我好想你
I miss you.
‎给我过来
Get back here!
‎起来 怎么样 不敢跟我打吗
Get up! What, are you scared to fight me?
‎害怕了吗
You scared?
‎起来打我啊 孬种
Get up and fight me, pussy! Pussy!
‎比利 过来 带你见个人
Billy, come over here, I want you to meet someone.
‎这是你妹妹 她叫麦克辛
This is your new sister. Her name's Maxine.
‎麦克斯
Max.
‎-握个手吧  -谁在那
-Shake her hand. - Who's there?
‎-叫你跟她握手  -谁在那
- I said, shake her hand. - I said, who's there?!
‎我好像找到了
I think I found it.
‎源头
The source.
‎在哪 小伊 你在哪
Where, El? Where are you?
布莱姆伯恩...
Brimborn...
炼钢厂
Steelworks.
‎这 好 炼钢厂 炼钢厂...
Here. Okay, uh, steelworks, steelworks...
‎这 炼钢厂
Here, steel.
‎找到了 樱桃橡树路 6522号
Found it. 6522 Cherry Oak Drive.
‎-很近  -小伊 我们找到了 快回来
-That's close. -El, El, we found it. Get out of there.
回来
Get out.
迈克
Mike?
Mike!
迈克
‎他听不见
He can't hear you.
‎你不应该去找我的
You shouldn't have looked for me.
‎因为我现在能看见你
Because now I see you.
‎我们都能看得见你
Now we can all see you.
‎你…
You...
‎让我们进来
let us in.
‎现在...
And now...
‎你得让我们留下来
you are going to have to let us stay.
大卫 你要去哪
David, where you going?
大卫
David?
‎亚当
Adam!
会错过烟花的
You're gonna miss it!
‎亚当
Adam!
‎看不出来吗
Don't you see?
一直
All this time,
‎我们一直在聚集力量
we've been building it.
‎我们聚集力量...
We've been building it...
‎都是为了你
for you.
那些努力
All that work,
‎那些痛苦
all that pain...
‎都是... 为了你
all of it... for you.
‎现在时间到了
And now it's time.
是时候结束了
Time to end it.
‎我们要杀了你
And we are going to end you.
‎等你死了
And when you are gone,
‎我们要杀了你的朋友们
we are going to end your friends.
‎-不要 -最后我们要杀了…
-No!  -And then we are going to end...
‎每个人
everyone.
‎走开
Get away!
‎不要
No!
‎你没事吧 小伊 怎么了
El, you're okay. It's...It's okay.
‎小伊
El.